Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Edward A. Feigenbaum papers
1950-2007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Feigenbaum, Edward A.
SC0340
86.5 Linear Feet and 89,702.3 megabytes
Collection primarily concerns his work in artificial intelligence at Stanford University and includes administrative files, correspondence, project files, trip files, proposals, reports, reprints, Artificial Intelligence Lab memos, audio tapes, video tapes, and files on computer programs, mainly DENDRAL, MOLGEN, ARPA, EPAM, and SUMEX.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Edward A. Feigenbaum.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research. The first two accessions have been digitized and are available online here: http://saltworks.stanford.edu/. For use of paper materials, requests must be made at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biography
Computer scientist. Feigenbaum received his B.S., 1956, and his Ph.D., 1959, in electrical engineering from Carnegie Institute of Technology. He completed a Fulbright Fellowship at the National Physics Laboratory and in 1960 went to the University of California, Berkeley, to teach in the School of Business Administration. He joined the Stanford faculty in 1965 in the Dept. of Computer Science; he served as Director of the Stanford Computation Center from 1965 to 1968 and as chairman of the Department from 1976 to 1981. Feigenbaum is a leading national figure in artificial intelligence and has developed computer resources for interactive research between medical and scientific collaborators on a national and global scale.
Scope and Content of Collection
Collection primarily concerns his work in artificial intelligence at Stanford University and includes administrative files, correspondence, project files, trip files, proposals, reports, reprints, Artificial Intelligence Lab memos, audio tapes, video tapes, and files on computer programs, mainly DENDRAL, MOLGEN, EPAM, and SUMEX. Also includes manuscript and published editions of his work Computers and Thought.
Audio recordings of Professor Feigenbaum discussing portions of the collection are available online: http://purl.stanford.edu/nk784qn9320.
Existence and Location of Copies
The first two accessions of the collection have been digitized and are available online here: http://saltworks.stanford.edu/.
Expert systems (Computer science); ARPANET (Computer network); Computer programs.; Artificial intelligence.; DENDRAL (computer programs).; Stanford University. Computer Science Department. Faculty; Lederberg, Joshua; Simon, Herbert Alexander; Feigenbaum, Edward A.
- Original accession, Accession ARCH-1986-052
  - Administrative records
    - SUMEX (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - SUMEX Site Visit, Sept. 14, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - SUMEX Executive Committee Meetings (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - SUMEX (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - SUMEX Proposal Budget, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - SUN Write-ups and View Graphs (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Survey of US C. S. Depts., Aug. 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Symbolic Computers/LISP Machine (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Symbolics (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - SUMEX--Equipment Acquisition Review (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Applications for SUMEX use (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - SUMEX Annual Report, May 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Sumex Renewal (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - S (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Switzerland Conference, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Tape Talks--Ed Feigenbaum (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Tarjan (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - NSF--Tarjan Award--12/31/76 Deadline (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Tektronix Visit, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - IJCAI Travel (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Teknowledge (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Telecon Minutes (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Terminal Inventory (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Terminals (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Allan Terry Thesis Proposal (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Thank You Letters (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Three Rivers Computer Corporation (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Tong, C. Thesis (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Feigenbaum Travel, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Using TYMNET (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - UNIVAC Nice, France Trip (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Typing Services (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Wiederhold, Gio. Response to peer review of project, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Lowell Wood (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Xerox Terminal (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Unit Editor System (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Hot File Visitors Mr. Bungers--Jan. 20, 1:30 P.M. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Visitors Control Situation (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Visitors Letters (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Visitor Letters, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Visiting Scholar Fumihiro Maruyama (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Visiting Professor Donald Michie, Fall 1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Budgets, 1973-76 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Building, 1975-78 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Space--M. Jacks Hall, architectural drawings, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Building Committee, 1974-79 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Computer Science at Stanford, report by Jonathan King, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Memos received, 1975-77 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Committee on Computer Science, 1972-75 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Visitor Letters, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Appointments and Promotions Committee [letters of inquiry for positions and lists of recent Ph.D's from other universities], 1979-80 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Appointments and Promotions Committee [letters of inquiry for positions and lists of recent Ph.D's from other universities], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Appointments and Promotions Committee [letters of inquiry for positions and lists of recent Ph.D's from other universities], 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - ARPA Proposal, 1974-75 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - HPP Proposal to ARPA, March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - ARPA Proposal, Jan. 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - ARPA Proposal, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - ARPA Contract--DAHC 15 73 C 0435 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - ARPA Contract, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - ARPA Knowledge Base (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Contracting Reports, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - ARPA Proposal, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - ARPA Proposal Background Material (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - ARPA Proposal, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - ARPA, 1974-76 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Appointments and Promotions Committee--Chronological File [letters of inquiry for positions and lists of recent Ph.D's from other universities], 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Appointments and Promotion Committee [letters of inquiry for positions and lists of recent Ph.D's from other universities], 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Appointments and Promotion Committee [letters of inquiry for positions and lists of recent Ph.D's from other universities], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Rand Calendar for, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Gray, Neil, 1977-79 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Green, Cordell, 1972-78 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Grinberg, Milt, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Guggenheim Fellowships (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - "H"--miscell. notes and correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Hardware brochures (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Harel, David: papers, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Hayashi Visit: correspondence and telex for visit of Hiromu Hayashi, Feb 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hearsay III: presentation notes, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - HPP Brochure: correspondence re: reprint permission for HPP brochure, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - HPP General: notes, acknowledgement of continuation proposal, HPP publication summary, 1973-77 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Heuristic Programming Project Letterhead: also note and diagrams for PLANNER (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Photos of EAF by Marek Majewski (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Copies of cover (unknown) for Computer Science (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - HPP Historical: miscellaneous notes and documents, 1976-81 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - HISTORY--Heuristic Programming Project: brochure on "Research in the Stanford Computer Science Department" and The Stanford Heuristic Programming Project: Goals and Activities 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - HPP Project: includes Introduction to HPP; note from Randall to EAF and Bruce Buchanan about problems with supervision in HPP; copy of award contract for HPP 1977; list of HPP personnel 1976. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - HPP Reviews (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - HPP Overviews, l976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - HPP Summary (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Humor (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Hydroid: Studies in Distributed Processing and Problem Solving. Binder containing notes, e-mail, copies of articles, 1976-77 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - "I" general correspondence, 1978-82 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - IBM: various correspondence, nominations for fellowships, symoposiums, etc., 1978-81 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - I E E E: reprint of "Digital Communications and the Conduct of Science: The New Literacy" by J. Lederberg, 1978. Request to EAF to write paper for I E E E. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Inada visit. Correspondence from Hiroshi Inada, Feb. 1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Interdepartmental requests (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Institute for Thought Research, Inc.: Copy of "Medical Research Proposal DSM III Project.", 1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - IJCAI-77 Aug 22-26, MIT: conference materials, paper "Knowledge Based Ship Classification," and correspondence, 1977-81 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Intel--corresp. re: symposium, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - ISI: Information Science Institute. Corresp. re: 10th anniversary presentation, proposal draft for Interlisp- like environment for LISP machine, etc., 1982 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - ISI -1975: Travel receipts, e-mail (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - ISI -1976: notes, bill for consulting (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - "J"--: Photocopy list of papers: AI Journal status as of Jan. 1, 1979, list of pending, sent back for revision, accepted, rejected (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Japanese Technology Transfer Institute: Correspondence re: study missions and possible tour of CS lab., 1981-2 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - The Japan Society of Northern Calif. :letter re: steering committee of South Bay area chapter., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science, Tokyo: Report to the Society by EAF on sponsored trip of Aug--Oct. 1979, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - "K": miscellaneous correspondence and resumes, 1976-78 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Lou Katz: resume and correspondence, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Knowledge Engineering for Medical Decision Making: draft and final version of paper, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Knutsen, Kjell, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - "L": Misc., 1976-79 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Keith Lantz, proposal on distributed computing at Stanford, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Lecture Bureau: promotional material from Leigh lecture bureau, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Irvine Lecture: Letter from Marty Belknap to EAF thanking him for being opening speaker, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Stanford Alumni Association--draft of article for Spring/Summer 1978 issue of The Stanford Magazine for Feigenbaum to correct, supplementary information (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Ohio State Distinguished Lecture Series Nov. 18, Correspondence regarding EAF's lecture, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - San Francisco State May 6.: Info regarding EAF talk on Information Science Curricula, 1976-1981 at SF State, May 6, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Carnegie-Mellon Lectures, Fall `76 (Traub, Kung): Infomation about EAF presenting Computer Science Lectures, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Immigration Course in Computer Science, Carnegie-Mellon U. Description of Immigration Course by Mary Shaw and H.T. Kung, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Lecture Notes: "Information Technology for Public Service" (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Lectures, misc: notes for talk at IBM Research, 4/12/78; seminar notice for Xerox PARC Sept. 9, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Elliot Levinthal, CV and articles, 1976-78 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Licensing: various licensing agreements and correspondence, 1981-83 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Licensing Agreement/OTL: info on Teknowledge licensing agreement (possible) for AGE-1 and EMYCIN, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Lindsay--proposal to SUMEX. reply to SUMEX-AIM Questionnaire and proposal., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - LOTS (Time Sharing): Correspondence between EAF, Ralph Gorin, and Miller on the establishment and augmentation of LOTS facility., 1976-77 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - "M": Miscellaneous correspondence, 1976-81 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - MCC Alpha Omega: copy of proposal (Alpha Omega) submitted to MCC [Microelectronics and Computer Consortium] by Gordon Bell, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - MCE--article from Electronics on proposed consortium Microelectronics and Computer Technologies Enterprises, March 10,1982 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Magazines: letters from Steve Lukasik, requesting EAF to be member of the Editorial board Information and Society, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Maheshwari, Arun (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Media. Requests for interviews with EAF, press clippings (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Medical Information Sciences: memos dealing with MIS committee, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Real-time Symbolic Computing Workshop. Cambridge, MA, Nov. 28-29, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - 5th Illinois Conference on Medical Info. Systems, May 3-4, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Yugoslavia Trip. Mailgram confirmation to MIT, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - IFIP Conference (Munich) Oct. 30--Nov. 1, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - National Advisory Council--Health. Oct. 21, 1978. (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - AIM Workshop (4th Annual) June 25-28, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - UCLA Short-course Program, (wk of May 22, 1978.) Information and travel arrangements for teaching "Decision making methods" (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Workshop on Application of Networking (D.C.) sponsored by NSF, May 8-9,1978 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Snowbird, Utah. Info. re: meeting organized by the Computer Science Board of the Chairmen of Ph.D. Granting Depts. of CS on July 10-11, 1978. (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Microcomputer Systems Proposal: Undergraduate Instructional Improvement Program, project for microcomputer Instructional facility, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Meta-EXEC Mitre Corp.: copy of ARC User Interface and corrections., 1976-77 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Misc. Magazine and Newspaper Clippings, 1976-83 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - P (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Permissions--Books (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - PERQ (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Percept-Image Physics Group (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Proposal--EAF Current Support, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Pople (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Van Dooren, Paul M. (Post-Doc) Autumn, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Chen, Hui-Chuan (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Prospective Article: What is Computer Science? (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - PUFF (NIH) (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - PUFF/VM: IMS Subcontract (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Gerry Purdy (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Feigenbaum Receipts (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - McGraw-Hill Royalties (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Fund Raising (Departmental Support Proposals Pending) (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Proposal Solicitations (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Protein Data Bank (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Publication Requests (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Purchase Requisitions (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Publications--EAF (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - PUFF/VM (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Q [Folder Empty] (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - AI--Qual (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - AI--Qual Reading (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - J. R. Quinlan Visiting Scholar (1978) (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Quote Requests (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - R (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Rabin Mini Course (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Rand Computer Use Contract (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Rand (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Rand Consulting (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Rees, Mina (Honoring) (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Release--Authors (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Requests with a No Response (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Requests for Meeting--No Response (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Requests for Reviews--No Response (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Requests for Visits--No Response (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - ROGET (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Paul Rosenbloom (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - S (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - SAIL Cost Center (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - SPO (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Support of Research on Expert Systems: A Proposal (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Schlumberger (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Schlumberger Proposal 1981 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Schlumberger Contract 1980 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Schlumberger--Permissions (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Schlumberger (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Vitae for Schwartz--Meeting of June 10: Degree Candidates (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Scientific American Article 1974 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - SIGBIO (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - SIMTEC (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Sloan Foundation (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Smart Systems Technology (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Snowbird 1980 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - SPL International (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - SRI Papers of W. F. Miller (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - SRI Seminar Series 1982 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - SRI Geology Program (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - SRI RA Support (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Stanford Text Network--1980 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Stanford University Board of Trustees Meeting--March 7, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Stanford University Memos--P I's (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Stanford University Memos--General (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Stauffer Foundation (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Steding, Tom (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Stefik/Expert Systems (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Stetson University Talk (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - SUMEX (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Computer Forum (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Computer Forum 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Computer Netwovtrking At Stanford (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Computing Reviews 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Consulting Policy (Stanford's) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Context Progress Reports (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - CROMEMCO (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - CSNET (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - D (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Data Products Printer Gift 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Dedication of Forsythe Hall 1/14/80 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Defense Science Board Summer Study (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - DENDRAL Book (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Development Office (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - King Plans (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Departmental Computer Acquisitions (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Digital Equipment Corporation--Relations (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - DoD Equipment Proposal (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Dolphin Interlisp Systems (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - E (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - ESL (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Earthquake Preparedness (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - EMYCIN AGE License (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Engineering Advisory Council (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Equipment--Automatic Dialers (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Expert System Workshop (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Report (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Meetings 1982-83 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Faculty Meetings 1980 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Seminars: Computers 1980 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, Etc. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1981 Jan 6 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1980 Sep (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Meetings (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - CS Staff Meeting Minutes (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Feigenbaum--Personal Memos (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Feigenbaum: Talks (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Fellowships (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Forum [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Forum [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Forsythe Award (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Forsywythe Lectures C. S. dept. (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - France Contacts (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Fujitsu (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Fujitsu--Training (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Task Force on the Future of Computing, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Task Force on the Future of Computing At Stanford (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Task Force on the Future of Computing at Stanford II (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Fund Raising (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - G (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Gardner Thesis (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Genet (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Ginzton Lab Committee (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Gifts (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Xerox Gift (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Gifts of Machines, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Graphics Devices (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Center for Integrated Systems (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Center for Law and Information Science (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Charles Babbage Institute Proposal (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - CIT (Formerly SCIP) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - CITATION Index Studies (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - COGNET (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Cognitive Science Computer Facility (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Cognitive Science Society (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Cognitive Sciences Society (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Cognitive Sciences (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Cognitive Science Society, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Cognitive Sciences (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Coinvestment Program (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - AIM Executive Committee Meeting File (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - CSL Meetings (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - HPP Executive Committee (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Missouri, University of--Health Care Advisory Committee (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - President's Advisory Committee, 1982 Dec 1 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - President's Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Computer Forum--Meeting, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Magazine/Newspaper Articles (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Music/Chowning: Negotiations (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - MOLGEN (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Mural (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - MYCIN (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - N (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - NIH (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - NIH Instructions, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Nixdorf (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - National Library of Medicine Program Project Support for Research (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - National Library of Medicine Proposal (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - UNC--Computer Science Evaluation March 28-30, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Northrop (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Notes on Knowledge Engineering and the HPP (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Nikkei Computer Article (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - NSF Instructions 1982 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - NSF--General (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - NSF Program (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - NSF Protein Cystallography (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - NSF Science in Developing Countries Program (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - NSF Special Committee on Computer Resources (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - NSF Testimony Feldman Report (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - A. I. Lab/NSF (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Stefik Paper to NSF (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - NSF Proposal Review (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - NSF Notices (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - NSF Site Visit--Feb. 24/25 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - NSF CS Advisory Committee Notices (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - O (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Oncocin Site Visits--Shortliffe (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Math Social Science Board, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Addenda to Computer Thought, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ARPANET (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - SUMEX Renewal, 1975-80 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - SUMEX Annual Report, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - SUMEX Annual Report, 1977-78 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stanford Artificial Intelligence Laboratory (SAIL) (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - SUMEX-AIM, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - CIS, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Postdoc Letters, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Grants, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Requests to Visit Stanford, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Satellite Business Systems: High Bandwidth Communication Link, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - NSF proposal for equipment, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - AI Laboratory Affairs, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)